getshogun.com 2017-05-20

# Shogun

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the www.getshogun.com and Shogun Labs, Inc and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Shogun Labs, Inc include www.getshogun.com and Shogun. The Shogun website is a Software as a Service site. By using the Shogun website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

### Collection of your Personal Information

Shogun may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. If you purchase Shogun's products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Shogun. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Shogun website.

Shogun encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Shogun so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Shogun is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Shogun website.

### Use of your Personal Information

Shogun collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.

Shogun may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Shogun and its affiliates. Shogun may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Shogun does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

Shogun may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Shogun, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Shogun will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Shogun or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Shogun; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Shogun, or the public.

### Security of your Personal Information

Shogun secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.

### Children Under Thirteen

Shogun does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

### Opt-Out & Unsubscribe

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from Shogun by contacting us here:

\- Web page: www.getshogun.com/contact

\- Email: admin@getshogun.com

### Changes to this Statement

Shogun will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Shogun encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Shogun is protecting your information.

### Contact Information

Shogun welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Shogun has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Shogun at:

Shogun Labs, Inc

47 Belcher Stre

San Francisco, California 94114

Email Address:

admin@getshogun.com

Effective as of March 11, 2015
